Chang (Michaux) Sun

5960 Student Union Blvd, Vancouver, BC, V6T 1Z1 778-681-5084 michaux2817@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/michaux-sun-1028

SUMMARY

A senior at UBC in a dual degree program - Computer Science (undergraduate) and Management (graduate). Proficient with Java, C++, SQL, and web programming. Strong communication, analytic and interpersonal skills from real industry working experience.

EDUCATION

University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC

Bachelor of Science + Master of Management Dual Degree (GPA 3.85) Completion: Dec 2022 Specialization: Computer Science

Langara College, Vancouver, BC

Computer Science Program (GPA 3.9)

Sep 2016 - Jul

WORK EXPERIENCE

LifeLabs - Head Office, Burnaby, BC

Developer (Co-op)

Sep 2019 - April 2020

GitHub: https://github.com/MichauxS-cc

- Created and launched a dynamic dashboard program independently to reflect real-time curriers specimen delivery activities on two physical locations (Burnaby & Surrey); (SQL query, external APIs, JavaScript, OOP)
- Built technical reports and customized Outlook add-in to achieved automation and digitalization of reports completing and sending for required departments; (VBA and TypeScript)
- Initiated business documentations to communicate with non-technical external suppliers

Tiger Applications LLC, Vancouver, BC

Junior Web Developer (Part-time)

Feb 2019 - Feb 2021

- Co-designed a website in a group of three; (JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Node, ¡Query)
- Deployed and maintained at least 10 web pages through XAMPP Web Server to run LESS files
- Implemented jQuery for additional slideshow functionality and mobile devices

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

- Frens (2021) Co-creator of the make-friends web application that generates friends list based on user input
 - My contributions include: implemented user authentication using jwt and local storage (salting & hashing password); implemented/intergraded Python script into the application to communicate with both front and backend; Main page functionalities and UI design; designed navigation bar for both desktop and mobile view
- Hogwarts (2021) Implemented and deployed a full-stack web application for Hogwarts magic school
 - Functionalities include allowing user to create study groups, editing group member info, checking core class info, and purchasing equipment by managing shopping cart (JavaScript, HTML/CSS, React, Express, Node, Redux, MongoDB, Heroku, Git)
- InsightUBC (2020) Co-designed a full-stack application for querying, displaying, scheduling UBC courses' and rooms' information; (Java, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, HTTP, REST)
- Memory Game (2018) Built a single/multi-player game to allow players to play games on the same computer; (Java, Sockets)

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

nwHacks Hackathon (University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC)

Jan 2020

Co-designed a web application (MongoDB, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, APIs) to generate vaccine recommendations for customers based on their injection history; learned how to use Standard Library to generate customized APIs

cmd-f Hackathon

48 hour all-female hackathon organized by Devpost - led group of 4 students, initiated and implemented a web application that allows user to control characters by speech recognition (Web Speech API, JavaScript)

DEF CON (Las Vegas, Nevada)

Sep 2016 - Jun 2017

Attended week-long conference; absorbed massive cutting-edge knowledge from tech experts; explored ethical hacking methods in various workshops

LANGUAGE AND TECHNOLOGIES

- Java | JavaScript | TypeScript | git | HTML | CSS | MongoDB | SQL | C | C++ | React | Node | VBA | JSON | APIs | Python
- Visual Studio | IntelliJ IDEA | WebStorm | Atom | Eclipse | Sublime | GitHub | XAMPP | cPanel

INTERESTS

Programming, Designing, Traveling (In-depth travel, visited over 6 countries, 30+ cities), Workout fanatic